// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which model shows a one-way communication where the source of information does not know whether the message is understood or not?",
    answer: "b. linear",
    options: [
      "a. interactive",
      "b. linear",
      "c. transactional",
      "d. a and b"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of a one-way communication?",
    answer: "a. a church leader giving a homily to a crowd of people",
    options: [
      "a. a church leader giving a homily to a crowd of people",
      "b. a teacher encouraging students to give their thoughts on a relevant issue",
      "c. classmates talking about how to accomplish their assignments",
      "d. all the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which model of communication shows the interchange of ideas among different individuals and shows progress in the process?",
    answer: "a. interactive",
    options: [
      "a. interactive",
      "b. linear",
      "c. transactional",
      "d. none of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Angie works for a fast food company as a cashier. A customer comes in to order sandwich and drinks. What model of communication is described in the given situation?",
    answer: "b. interactive",
    options: [
      "a. conversational",
      "b. interactive",
      "c. linear",
      "d. transactional"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following elements affects the flow of any communication process?",
    answer: "a. barrier",
    options: [
      "a. barrier",
      "b. channel",
      "c. feedback",
      "d. source"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which element is NOT found in Shannon-Weaver model?",
    answer: "d. receiver",
    options: [
      "a. barrier",
      "b. channel",
      "c. feedback",
      "d. receiver"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "You and your neighbors would like to initiate a project for the benefit of the elderly in your community. The chairman presented his proposal and ignored his constituents’ suggestions. What model of communication is presented here?",
    answer: "a. Berlo’s Model",
    options: [
      "a. Berlo’s Model",
      "b. Shannon-Weaver Model",
      "c. Schramm Model",
      "d. Transactional Model"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In the situation found in number 7, what element of communication is missing?",
    answer: "c. feedback",
    options: [
      "a. barrier",
      "b. context",
      "c. feedback",
      "d. receiver"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "When is communication considered a failure?",
    answer: "b. Both sender and receiver stopped the conversation process.",
    options: [
      "a. A negative feedback was given by the recipient of the message.",
      "b. Both sender and receiver stopped the conversation process.",
      "c. The persons involved fixed the problem that was created in the process.",
      "d. The recipient did not decode the meaning of the message sent."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a purpose of communication?",
    answer: "a. It creates blunder that worsens an existing issue or concern.",
    options: [
      "a. It creates blunder that worsens an existing issue or concern.",
      "b. It fosters good relationship among people.",
      "c. It gears towards the solution to a problem.",
      "d. It gives an overview of a national issue for public understanding."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of an interactive communication?",
    answer: "c. A TV anchor interviews lawmakers about the MECQ in the metro.",
    options: [
      "a. A barker persuades the commuters to take a jeepney going to Pacita Complex.",
      "b. A social media influencer gets a million views from her debut video.",
      "c. A TV anchor interviews lawmakers about the MECQ in the metro.",
      "d. A vendor starts a small talk with his customer and the latter gives in to it."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "A friend’s Facebook status caught your attention. It is intended for you. It is personally attacking you. To put the purpose of communication into context, what is the best thing that you should do?",
    answer: "c. Talk to the concerned person privately to settle the conflict",
    options: [
      "a. Immediately comment on his/her status with provocative words",
      "b. Inform him/her that you are going to sue him/her in court",
      "c. Talk to the concerned person privately to settle the conflict",
      "d. Tell the public about his/her dishonest way of life"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which communication model is dynamic where the process does not stop after one has given feedback and continues to progress as topics and persons involved may change overtime, too?",
    answer: "c. transactional",
    options: [
      "a. interactive",
      "b. linear",
      "c. transactional",
      "d. A and C"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "On your way home, you dropped by a convenient store. Queuing to pay for some essentials, you heard a customer arguing with the cashier. The customer talked on top of his voice complaining for something you could not clearly hear. The buyer next to him interrupted the one complaining. The others in the line could not help but gave their own sides of the story. Finally, the manager came in. What model of communication is presented in the entire scenario?",
    answer: "d. transactional",
    options: [
      "a. interactive",
      "b. linear",
      "c. occasional",
      "d. transactional"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "From the given situation above, what should the manager do?",
    answer: "d. Respectfully pull out the customer and look for a win-win solution to the problem.",
    options: [
      "a. Arrogantly confront the customer for being tough",
      "b. Publicly reprimand the cashier to show that the customer is always right",
      "c. Tell the other customers to stop gossiping",
      "d. Respectfully pull out the customer and look for a win-win solution to the problem."
    ]
  },
];
